<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: security | 0xNaN]]></title>
  <link href="http://0xNaN.github.io/blog/categories/security/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://0xNaN.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-06-11T00:16:15+02:00</updated>
  <id>http://0xNaN.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[NaN]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two words about security]]></title>
    <link href="http://0xNaN.github.io/blog/2013/10/12/two-words-about-security/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-12T20:06:00+02:00</updated>
    <id>http://0xNaN.github.io/blog/2013/10/12/two-words-about-security</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Few days ago I bought an item from a <em>famous</em> online shop.<br />
This site provides a simple game that allows to win points, which afterwards the users can transform to coupons.<br />
It consist in a simple animation which shift 12 baskets from right to the left: the user must shoots a ball and hit the center of the basket.  <!--More -->
Each basket provides points according to is own dimension: if it’s tiny the user gets a lot of points, otherwise he gets less points.<br />
When the time ends, the user can transform the points to coupons: 100pnt for <strong>1$</strong> (for purchases over 10$), 300pnt for <strong>3$</strong>(for purchases over 30$), 4000pnt for <strong>15$</strong>(for purchases over 150$), and so on.<br />
The graphics of the game is really nice and there are a lot of nice effects with HD images.<br />
The game is written in HTML and CSS and the baskets are hidden trough CSS (<code>display</code> propriety), also the value of each basket is set trough a CSS class.<br />
When I saw this I wanted to try a stupid test: change the value of CSS class trough the DevTools of Chrome and run the game.<br />
The result? I’ve completed the game with an incredible amount of points and the server didn’t noticed it!! I was able to trasform all the points to coupons and use them.<br />
This reminded me how much stupid people care about the graphics, forgetting the security of the code, even though there are real money in prize!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
